export const data = [
    {
        question: "A state in React.js is also known as?",
        option1: "Permanent storage ",
        option2: "External storage of a component",
        option3: "The internal storage of the component",
        option4: "All of the above",
        ans: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is used in React.js to increase performance?",
        option1: "preventDefault()",
        option2: "avoidDefault()",
        option3: "revokeDefault()",
        option4: "None of the above",
        ans: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "JSX stands for ___",
        option1: "Javascript and AngularJS",
        option2: "JSON",
        option3: "JSON XML",
        option4: "Javascript XML",
        ans: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "Identify the one which is used to pass data to components from outside?",
        option1: "Render with arguments",
        option2: "setStates",
        option3: "props",
        option4: "PropTypes",
        ans: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "Identify the command used to create a react app?",
        option1: "npm install create-react-app",
        option2: "install -g create-react-app",
        option3: "npm install -g create-react-app",
        option4: "none of the above",
        ans: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "How many elements can a valid react component return?",
        option1: "1",
        option2: "2",
        option3: "3",
        option4: "4",
        ans: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "Who created React.js?",
        option1: "Jordan Mike",
        option2: "Jordan Walke",
        option3: "Tim Lee",
        option4: "Jordan Lee",
        ans: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "In which language is React.js written?",
        option1: "Python",
        option2: "Javascript",
        option3: "Java",
        option4: "PHP",
        ans: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "What is Babel?",
        option1: "Javascript compiler",
        option2: "Javascript interpreter",
        option3: "Javascript transpiler",
        option4: "None of the above",
        ans: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "Identify the smallest building block of React.JS.",
        option1: "Props",
        option2: "Elements",
        option3: "State",
        option4: "Components",
        ans: 4,
    }

]